Finding Aid of the Society of American Archivists Records, 1935-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1935-2016, UWM Manuscript Collection 172; 271.9 cubic ft. (385 boxes, including 16 audio cassettes and 33 videocassettes) 1 oversize folder 7,545 digital files (26.2 GB) 1 film reel 5 microfilm reels approximately 170 books and serial titles
  - 8. Units, 200/08
    - 1. Committees, 1944-2013, 200/08/01; 27.4 cubic ft. (37 boxes)
      - Education and Professional Development Committee, 1965-1993
        - Papers, 1986-1992 (Box 24, Folder 30)
        - Practicum Guidelines, 1988-1991 (Box 24, Folder 31)
        - Practicum, Program Standard for Archival Education, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 32)
        - Program Session at Annual Meeting, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 20)
        - Questionnaires, 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
        - Reports, 1986-1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
        - Self-Study, 1979-1986 (Box 25, Folder 3)
        - Self-Study Reports
          - Auburn University, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
          - Case Western University, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
          - Michigan State University, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 17)
          - New York University, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 18)
          - State University of New York--Albany, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 19)
          - Temple University, Urban Archives Center, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 20)
          - University of Illinois--Urbana Champaign, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
          - University of Louisville, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 12)
          - University of Maryland, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 13-15)
          - University of Michigan, Bentley History Library, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 16)
          - University of Texas--Arlington, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 21)
          - University of Western Ontario, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 22)
          - Western Washington University, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 23)
        - Single Course Offerings, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
        - Standards Board Proposal, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 5)
        - Suggested Archival Components in the Library School Curriculum, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 23)
        - Survey of Archival Training Institutes, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 21)
        - Survey of Single Course Offerings, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 22)
        - Training Project, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - Western Washington University Education Conference, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
        - Workshop Publication Advisory Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Emergency Activities Committee, 1951-1952
        - Sherrod East, 1951-1952 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Finding Aids Committee, 1975-1977
        - Survey and Report of Task Force on Accession Reports of Repositories, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 13-14)
      - Goals and Priorities Committee, 1982-1996
        - An Action Agenda for the Archival Profession: Institutionalizing the Planning Process, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 2)
        - Agendas, Correspondence, Minutes, Three-year Vision Statement, 1989-1991 (Box 35, Folder 3)
        - AHA Newsletter, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 7)
        - Annual Report, 1987-1989 (Box 25, Folder 8)
        - Automation Planning Group, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 9)
        - Background, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence, 1982-1991 (Box 25, Folder 11-20)
        - Correspondence, "Filling the GAP: Planning on Local and Individual Levels," 1985 (Box 25, Folder 21)
        - Five-Year Assessment, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 22)
        - Goals and Objectives, 1983-1985 (Box 25, Folder 23)
        - Grants, 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 24)
        - Historians' Reactions, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 25)
        - Initial Discussion Draft, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 26)
        - Initiatives, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 27)
        - Leadership Forum, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 28)
        - Meetings, 1985-1991, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 29)
        - Members, 1983-1990 (Box 25, Folder 30)
        - NHPRC Grant, 1989-1991 (Box 35, Folder 4)
        - NHPRC Program Emphases, 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 31)
        - Papers, 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 32)
        - Planning Group, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 33)
        - Planning Group, Reports, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 34)
        - Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 35)
        - Proposals, National Congress on Historical Records, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 36)
        - Report, Archival Activity in the United States Since Publication of Planning for the Archival Profession, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 5)
        - Report, Reactions/Comments, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 5)
        - Reports, 1984-1991 (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
        - Reports, "Action Agenda," 1988 (Box 26, Folder 4)
        - Strategic Planning, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
        - 2020 Vision, 1989-1992 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Government and Archives Joint Committee, 1987-1988
        - Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 31)
      - Historians and Archivists Joint Committee, 1988
        - Annual Report, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 32)
      - Institutional Evaluation and Development Committee, 1989-1991
        - Background, 1989-1991 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Intergovernmental Relations Committee, 1967-1971
        - Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 26)
        - Commission Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - Data, Profiles on Individuals, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
        - Membership, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
        - Program Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
        - Proposals for Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
        - U.S. Government Dossier, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - International Archival Affairs Committee, 1973-1998
        - Annual Report, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 2)
        - Annual Report, 1987-1990 (Box 26, Folder 15)
        - Correspondence, 1987-1998 (Box 26, Folder 16-20)
        - "Heiner Affair," 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 21)
        - Latin American Initiative, 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 22)
        - Meetings, 1987-1998 (Box 26, Folder 23)
        - Members, 1991-1995 (Box 26, Folder 24)
        - Newsletters, 1987-1996 (Box 26, Folder 25)
        - Operations Manual, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 26)
        - Recommendations to Council, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 27)
        - Requests for Assistance, 1994-1997 (Box 26, Folder 28)
        - Study Tour, 1973-1975 (Box 32, Folder 3)
        - Three-year Plan, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 29)
        - World View, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 30)
      - Labor Archives Committee, 1973-1976
        - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
        - Subject Files, Survey of American Labor Resources, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Legal and Legislation Issues Committee, 1979-1994
        - 102d Congress, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 33)
        - Authorization Legislation, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 34)
        - Copyright, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 35)
        - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 36)
        - "Fair Use" Provisions, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 37)
        - Funding for NARA and NHPRC, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 38)
        - GPO Gateway to Government Act, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 39)
        - GPO WINDO, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 40)
        - Guidelines and Procedures, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 41)
        - JFK Records, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 42)
        - Members, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 43)
        - NARA, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 44)
        - NHPRC, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 45)
        - Nixon Tapes, 1979-1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - Nixon Tapes and White House E-mail Report, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 2)
        - NUCMC, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 4)
        - Three-Year Plan, 1991-1994 (Box 27, Folder 5)
        - White House E-Mail, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1972-1983
        - Ads and Exhibits Committee, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 28)
        - Archivist Song, Garrison Keillor, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 17)
        - Budget and SAA Fund, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 14)
        - Chair, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 13)
        - General Files, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 27)
        - General Files, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
        - General Files, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Manuscripts and Special Collections Committee, 1967-1969
        - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 28-29)
      - Membership Committee, 1978-1995, 2001-2006
        - Agendas, Correspondence, Reports, 2001-2006 (Box 35, Folder 6)
        - Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
        - Goals and Guidelines, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 10)
        - Key Contact Program, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 11)
        - Meetings, 1988-1990 (Box 27, Folder 12)
        - Members, 1978-1994 (Box 27, Folder 13)
        - Proposal, Membership Campaign, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 14)
        - Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 27, Folder 15)
        - Review of Activities, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 16)
        - Questionnaire, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Membership Development Committee, 1963-1964
        - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Microforms Committee, 1957-1965
        - Correspondence and Working Papers, 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence and Working Papers, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Municipal Records Committee, 1953-1957
        - Correspondence, 1953-1957 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Network Advisory Committee, 1988-1989
        - Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Nominating Committee, 1949-2014
        - Annual Meeting Work Packet, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 24)
        - Annual Report, 1986-1989 (Box 27, Folder 19)
        - Ballot, Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 35, Folder 7)
        - Bulletins, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 19)
        - Candidates, 1982-1990 (Box 27, Folder 20-22)
        - Candidates, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 23)
        - Candidates, Harold T. Pinkett, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 24)
        - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 27)
        - Correspondence, 1980-1990 (Box 27, Folder 25-26)
        - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 27)
        - Correspondence, Candidates, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 25)
        - Council Nominees, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 29)
        - Elections, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 28)
        - Elections, 1980-1986 (Box 27, Folder 29)
        - Elections, 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 30)
        - Elections, 2011
        - Elections, 2012
        - Elections, 2013
        - Elections, 2014
        - Final Report, 1987-1990 (Box 27, Folder 31)
        - Forms and Guide Letters, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 26)
        - General Files, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 32)
        - General Files, 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 5-8)
        - Guidelines and Procedures, 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 32)
        - Guidelines and Procedures, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 33)
        - Guidelines and Procedures, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 34)
        - Manuscript and Repositories Steering Committee, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 35)
        - Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 36)
        - Meetings, 1984-1990 (Box 27, Folder 37)
        - Potential Candidates, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 28)
        - Report, 1990, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 38)
        - Report, "Why Members Decline the Presidential Nomination," 1998 (Box 27, Folder 39)
        - Sherrod East, 1949-1953 (Box 32, Folder 20)
        - Treasurer Nominees, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 30)
        - Vice President Nominees, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - Oral History Committee, 1969-1978
        - General Files, 1969-1978 (Box 11, Folder 3-6)
      - Photographic Techniques Committee, 1949
        - Sherrod East, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Preservation Publication Award Committee, 2001-2003 (Electronic \Preservation Publications Award Committee 2001-2003\)
      - Professional Standards Committee, 1983-1994
        - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box 27, Folder 40)
        - Fellowship Nominations, 1983-1988 (Box 27, Folder 41-45)
        - Guidelines, 1990-1994 (Box 32, Folder 21)
        - Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 22)
        - Reports, 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 46)
      - Professional Standards and Training Committee, 1966-1983
        - Election of Fellows, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - General Files, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
        - General Files, 1978-1982 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
        - General Files, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 4)
        - Nominations of Fellows, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Program Committee, 1962-1983
        - 1962-1964
          - Chair's Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 7-9)
          - Chair's Correspondence with Other Committee Chairs, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
          - Chair's Correspondence with Program Participants, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        - 1970 (Box 11, Folder 15)
        - 1980
          - Administration, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
          - Correspondence and Working Papers, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
          - Final Sessions, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
          - Plenary; Seminars, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
          - Program Drafts, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 9)
          - Proposed Sessions, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 10)
          - Reports of the 1979 Program, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 11)
        - 1981
          - Correspondence, General, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
          - Correspondence, Sessions and Evaluations, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
          - Guidelines, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
          - Ideas for Sessions, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
          - Local Arrangements, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
          - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
          - Session Proposals, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 7-9)
          - Sessions Planned by Fleckner, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
        - 1982
          - Committee Meeting, 1981 November (Box 10, Folder 25)
          - Committee Meeting at 1981 Annual Meeting, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
          - Committee Members' Files, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
          - Correspondence from Committee Members, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
          - Correspondence with SAA Office, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
          - Evaluations, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 26)
          - General Files, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 17)
          - Hackman File Regarding Sessions, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 18)
          - Hackman Speech to Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 24)
          - Ideas for Sessions, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 19)
          - Local Arrangements, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 20)
          - Mailings to Committee, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 21)
          - Planning, Seminars and Workshops on, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 22)
          - Program Suggestions, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 23)
          - Revised Copy for Program, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
        - 1983 (Linda Henry's Files)
          - Analysis of 1982 Meetings, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 5)
          - Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 6-8)
          - Correspondence Regarding Specific Sessions, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 9)
          - Luncheon Talk, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
          - Meetings (Agenda, Handouts, Notes), 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 11)
          - Participants (Women, Minorities, and Newcomers), 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
          - Pre-rating System and Suggestions for Next Chair, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 13)
          - Proposals, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
          - Ratings, Analysis, and Comments, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Public Information Committee, 1988-1996
        - Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 27, Folder 47)
        - News Clippings, 1990-1993 (Box 27, Folder 48-51)
        - News Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 1-4)
        - News Clippings, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
        - News Clippings, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Publications Committee, 1978-1980
        - Archivist's Catalog, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - College and University Section Steering Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 4-5)
        - Directories, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - Grants Manual, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Publicity Committee, 1944-1969
        - Annual Meeting Program, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
        - Biographical and Press Releases, Working Papers, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        - Chair, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        - Chair, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
        - Newspaper Clippings Regarding Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        - Press Releases Regarding Fellows, Miscellaneous Publicity Materials, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        - Sherrod East, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Records and Professional Organizations Committee, 1963-1964
        - Index, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 9)
        - Project Study, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 10)
        - Questionnaire, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Records Management Committee, 1957-1969
        - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        - Correspondence, Session at Annual Meeting, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        - Correspondence and Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 19)
        - Correspondence and Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - Miscellaneous, 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Reference, Access and Photoduplication Policies Committee, 1970-1974
        - General Files, 1970-1974 (Box 39, Folder 1-6)
      - Reference and Access Policies Committee, 1974-1976
        - General Files, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
        - Survey on User, Mail Order, Reproduction Fees, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
      - Regional Archival Activity Committee, 1973-1990
        - Annual Report, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 32, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 13)
        - Directory, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 14)
        - General Files, 1973-1982 (Box 11, Folder 7)
        - Guidelines, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 15)
        - Meetings, 1986-1989 (Box 29, Folder 16)
        - Members, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
        - Mission and Purpose, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 9)
        - Newsletter, 1986-1988 (Box 29, Folder 17)
        - Reports, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - Survey of Outreach Activity, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Religious Archives Committee, 1949-1978
        - Correspondence, 1958-1967 (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
        - Correspondence, 1968-1973 (Box 34, Folder 1-3)
        - Directory, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - General Committee Objectives, 1973-1978 (Box 34, Folder 5)
        - General Files, 1961-1967 (Box 7, Folder 13)
        - General Files, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 14)
        - General Files, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
        - General Files, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
        - General Files, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 17)
        - General Files, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
        - General Files, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 19)
        - Guide, 1966-1968 (Box 34, Folder 6)
        - Membership Roster, 1959-1978 (Box 34, Folder 7)
        - Miscellaneous Publications and Directory, 1949-1962 (Box 7, Folder 12)
        - Proposals, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 8)
        - Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 9)
        - Workshop, 1965-1971 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Resolutions Committee, 1968-1975
        - Correspondence, Meetings, Reports, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 18)
        - Lists, Deceased Members, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - SAA/AAM/AASLH Joint Committee on Opportunities for Minorities in Museums, 1980-1985
        - Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 29, Folder 19)
        - Reports and Surveys, 1980-1985 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Selection of Archival Fellows Committee, 1991-1994
        - General File, 1991-1994 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Standards Committee, 2005-2009
        - Archival Facilities Subcommittee, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - Minutes and Reports, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - Minutes and Reports, 2006-2007 (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - Minutes and Reports, 2008-2009 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - State and Local Records Committee, 1962-1978
        - Correspondence, Directory of State and Provincial Archives, 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, General and Membership, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 16)
        - Directory, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 1)
        - General Files, 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 21)
        - General Files, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 33)
        - Local and Public Records, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 17)
        - Local Records Survey, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 22)
        - Newsletter, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 23)
        - Posner Project Update, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 18)
        - "Priorities for Local Records," Conference on Priorities, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 24)
        - Projects, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 19)
        - Questionnaires, Directory of State and Provincial Archives, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
        - Report, Records Retention and Disposition Schedules, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 24)
        - Subcommittee on Local Public Records, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Status of the Profession Committee, 1970-1978
        - Correspondence, 1973-1976, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
        - Personnel Questionnaire, Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 5-8)
        - Roster, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
        - Salary Survey, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
        - Survey of State Agencies, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Status of Women in the Archival Profession Committee, 1970-1997
        - ALA Status of Women in Librarianship
          - Annual Meetings, 1979-1982 (Box 16, Folder 1)
          - Correspondence, 1977-1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
          - Directory of Professional Women's Groups, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
          - General Literature, 1980-1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
        - Childcare at Annual Meetings, Development, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 5)
        - Committee Guidelines, 1973, 1983, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 7-10)
        - Correspondence, 1976-1989 (Box 17, Folder 1-8)
        - Correspondence, 1990-1997 (Box 18, Folder 1)
        - EEO (Equal Employment Opportunity) Monitoring Project
          - Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 18, Folder 2)
          - Reports and Literature, 1970-1983, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
          - Survey of State Agencies, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
        - Equal Rights Amendment and the SAA, 1979-1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
        - General File, 1974-1997 (Box 30, Folder 2-3)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1978-1983 (Box 18, Folder 6)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1991-1997 (Box 18, Folder 7)
        - Membership Lists, 1980-1998, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
        - Membership Survey, 1971-1973, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
        - Profile Report to SAA Council, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 10)
        - Report, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 18)
        - SAA Fellows, Gender Studies, 1983, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 11)
        - SAA Fellows, Nominations, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 12)
        - SAA Program and Workshop Proposals, 1981-1988 (Box 18, Folder 13-14)
        - Salary Survey of the Archival Profession, Correspondence, 1977-1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
        - Salary Survey of the Archival Profession, Professional Literature, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 2)
        - Salary Survey of the Archival Profession, Surveys and Reports, 1976-1982 (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - Task Force on Organizational Effectiveness Recommendations, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 4)
        - Twentieth Anniversary, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 5)
        - Women's Roster, 1976-1979, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 6-10)
      - Symposia Coordinating Committee, 1972-1975
        - General Files, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 8-9)
      - Techniques for the Control and Description of Archives and Manuscripts Committee, 1969-1974
        - Draft Standards, undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
        - General File, 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 10)